This is Trigun.
guitar solo
A $700,000 double-dollar reward for the
escaped convicts of the Nebraska family.
That is huge.
Don't waste your time.
Take that one down. But why?
Because they were caught.
Huh?
Wow, it's only been five hours
since the warrant was issued.
That has to be the record.
You'll be even more surprised
when you see who caught them.
The entire city of an April?
What is this?
it's true just like it says the
entire city probably jumped in that
is a whole lot of divvying must be
populated by a bunch of macho types
are you really sure about this
after all the entire town did try to
kill you and you are the one who
single-handedly defeated the Nebraska
family so why did you pass up
the seven hundred thousand double
dollars well why not oh a big pile
of money like that Would just be a
nuisance to a careless drifter like
me and besides now I get to have
all the salmon sandwiches I could
possibly eat isn't that right grams.
Oh, yeah, darn tootin.
I'm kind of jealous
You could have bought all the sandwich
factories with money like that.
Oh
Well, then are you gentlemen
finished with your talk?
Why yes Then I would suggest that you
get away from him as soon as you can.
After all, this man is Bash the Stampede!
He's dangerous, you
know, isn't that right?
Well, yeah.
Hmm.
Why did it have to be him?
Make way! Make way!
Step aside, please!
The infamous outlaw Bash the
Stampede is coming through!
He's a wanted man with a bounty on his
head for 60 billion double dollars!
Feared everywhere!
As the humanoid typhoon, watch out!
Because the legendary ace gunman!
Folks, if you come near
him and he bites you,
don't expect your insurance to cover it!
You know, I was just wondering, how long
are you guys planning on hanging around?
Well, always, Mr.
Vash.
You see, as insurance
society representatives,
it's our assignment to curb the damages.
in the cases where you're involved.
Isn't that right, Meryl?
Yeah, that's right.
Just what in the hell do
you have to be upset about?
Do you have any idea how much money the
society lost because of
the crap you've pulled?
Now, now, stop that.
I found you, Vash the Stampede!
It's a bounty hunter!
You'll have to do better than that.
Right, I thought we were
gonna get you, Vash.
I guess I'm just lucky that
these girls aren't too swift,
if you know what I'm saying.
I understand how you feel,
but this is not the answer.
You have to try to calm down.
It's the sand steamer!
Yahoo!
Time to make some money!
Wow, it's a humpback glass steamer.
Oh my gosh, that thing is gigantic.
I've never seen such a huge sand steeple.
It's really incredible. I know.
Millie? Hmm?
Where did Bash go?
He's gone.
What do you think we should do?
What do you think?
Hey, hey, hey!
Look at this!
You've never seen anything like it!
Check this out!
It's the latest tasseled beagle!
How about this one?
Are you nuts?
They're worth way more than that.
Hey, mister, do you need
an extra hard worker today?
I could use an extra pair
of hands, but not a kid's.
This is like a big annual
community festival.
The timing couldn't be better.
All of the plant engineers that we
contacted arrived on the steamer,
and we have more than enough to pay them.
Looks like my idea of calling in the
Nebraska family saved the day after all.
Yeah, right, but one false move
would have meant utter disaster.
You're no fun.
Huh?
Whoa, there's a total babe on this ship.
She is so beautiful.
Hey, hey, goddess girl.
Would you like to go out on a date, huh?
Hey, I'm the guy who's in
charge of this fine city.
Hey, don't be like that.
Hey, come on, babe.
Give me a chance.
Hey, don't you know I'm
supersonic Sodom the Great? Huh?
Perhaps it's better if you're
not too familiar with me.
Oh, my goodness.
You were just tired.
Okay.
Vash the Stampede.
Age unknown, origin unknown.
No permanent address.
Wanted for the murder
of Count Lebnant Vazquez
and under suspicion of
class G weapon damage.
They will pay sixty billion double
dollars for you dead or alive!
I know everything about you mr.
Vash the Stampede that
makes it so much easier.
Let's get married right now.
What do you say?
Wonderful proposal you like that, huh,
but I have you at a disadvantage
You don't know anything about me.
Aren't you curious a little?
Hmm.
I already can tell a lot about you
You happen to be a woman who by chance
had her heart stolen by a stoic peace-loving
gunman In a word a pretty fairy.
My name is Elizabeth I happen
to be the chief engineer
of the Marius Breskin can
tackle technical industrial
union work dispatch team
So in short you're a fairy
like plant engineer then you
know anything about plants.
Mr. Bash, huh?
Aren't they like lost technology from
over a hundred years ago or something?
That's right.
They are systems which can achieve
production beyond all theoretical law.
They are the leftovers from
the Pandora's box God gave
us that allow you and I to
exist in this poor environment.
I came to this place to repair the plant
and to keep that hope
alive for these people.
Then will you marry me?
First, I have a special job
I want you to do for me.
Is there some kind of reward?
Don't worry.
I will give you what you want.
What I want? Really? Really? I'll do it!
I'll do it!
I'll do whatever you want!
Over here!
Everything is dark cheap!
Here's a piping hot one
fresh out of the oven!
Oh, dude!
It smells delicious!
For crying out loud, where the
hell did that man run off to now?
Yeah, all of these extra people
here makes it hard to find him.
That doesn't mean he'd be in there.
Keep looking, Millie.
Whoa!
Hello there, cute pie.
I'm ready and willing to be
your obedient little doggy.
I respond well to discipline.
Nice try, punk, but you're just a child.
Yeah?
That's right.
She may not look it, but she's 20.
Millie, he doesn't need to know that.
Yeah, I'd advise against it anyway, pal.
She's really bitchy.
What did you say?
Mr. Vash.
What? Vash?
Where the hell have you been?
What have you...
Who may I ask is that a total babe that is
not what I mean I asked him to serve as my
personal Bodyguard
while I'm here to revise
the plant system program
Oh come along the spot
Spa where's the hotel it's just
up ahead we're almost there
master thank you well we did find
Him that is good isn't it um I'd
rather do a mountain of paperwork
than watch over that idiot
for one more second I'm beginning
the restoration work at 6 a .m.
sharp so spot don't be late
not to worry ma 'am in some
places I'm known as rooster
boy or early bird or even mr.
up-and-at-um hey are we in the
same room as soon as my Work is done.
Spot until then, you are going
to sleep in the innermost room?
Good night.
Now never seems to go my way. Hmm.
Something's coming!
Stop there!
I don't like sleeping with
men, especially ugly ones.
Would you please be good enough to go now?
He actually did what I asked him.
Ah, what happened here?
This is horrible!
Oh, hi, nothing to worry about.
Go back to sleep.
Oh, my God, it's Vash's stampede!
I'm glad that I took the time to switch
our room numbers in the hotel registry.
That's no fair.
Aren't you protecting me?
I'd at least like to hear an explanation.
Tomorrow will do.
I lost my room, so can I share yours?
But you have a bed right out there.
That's so cold.
I'm sure I'm glad you
Bernardelli people are here.
Here's my insurance policy.
By the way, for our records,
who was staying in this room?
Can't you tell by looking at the damage?
It was Vasta Stampede, of course.
Uh, yeah, that guy.
There can only be one reason why
someone is trying to kill me.
Most of what created the
plant was lost technology.
And I have the knowledge to use it.
But that doesn't necessarily mean that I
completely understand
what the plant really is.
Well, how have you
managed up to this point?
The union has always provided an escort
for me in case there was any trouble.
But this time, isn't it
wonderful you were here for me?
I'll do my best to live
up to your expectations.
Hey, you!
You can't come in here!
This area's restricted!
I found out you're the one
responsible for the hotel explosion.
Well, you found out wrong.
It was your fault, wasn't it?
The chief is gonna get mad at
us for not doing our job again.
But I was the victim in all this.
Besides, you're not
really crying, are you?
Anyway, this plant is an important place,
and you are not allowed to be in here.
But I really need him here.
After all, Scott is guarding me.
Well, he may appear to be harmless,
but he's bashed the stampede, you know.
That's exactly why I need him.
But don't you understand?
Wherever this man goes, he
always leaves trouble behind him.
Chief, there's a malfunction
in section number three.
Gee, what amazing timing. No!
I don't get it.
The production system in plant number
four suddenly started operating.
Shut down the main control.
Yes, ma 'am.
It's no good.
It's not shutting down.
This is really bad.
We're going to have to send the
plant all the new data directly.
Spot? Yes! Come.
Coming! Wait a minute.
Where are you going?
Try to understand.
Even if I have to shake you
from me, I've got to go!
There's definitely something wrong with
the dynamics of the situation here.
I think we'd better take shelter.
There's trouble already
swarming after him.
Flip the switch. Right!
Right away. I'm on it.
Run!
Can't you run?
Nice warm-up. Now let's play.
I don't understand how you got in
here, my vicious little friend.
It's a mystery to me.
You're actually kind of cute.
I guess I'll have to get
someone better to beat you.
It looks like I'll have to do it myself.
Hey!
What did you do that for?
Am I being punished for something?
I want you dead.
Oh, are you after that stupid reward? No.
I want you to die for what you did on
Stardate 0104, July City, 2.06 p .m.
Don't you remember?
I'd think that you would
because that was the
day that you earned your
first criminal record.
That's right.
That day you transformed the
third city of July, my hometown,
into nothing less than hell itself.
I don't know what kind
of witchcraft you used.
The city was so badly destroyed,
and yet no one was killed.
But do you know what happened after?
One million four hundred thousand
people became homeless and destitute.
Their bodies and souls
parched to the bone.
They abused each other, stole from
each other, and despised one another.
That's right,
because of you I was thrown into
hell, but I still had to go on living.
Mommy! Daddy!
Why aren't you moving?
I remember it like it was yesterday,
wandering through the rubble of what
used to be a city at the age of three.
I want you to experience the
same pain and sadness I felt.
It's your turn.
Now is the time to avenge
my mother and father.
Repent.
Repent and die!
Bash the stampede!
The same thing I can do.
It's no good, the power
levels aren't dropping.
If we don't control it, in a few
hours it'll trigger an overflow,
then meltdown time.
Fire has erupted and spread
into the Animus class.
If it explodes it'll leave a crater
200 yards wide I input the new data.
How are the power?
Everyone evacuate the facility quickly.
Yes, ma 'am
He decided to stay
behind what that's right.
He's decided to stay out of it, but it's
not necessary for him to stay behind
I'm gonna go get him back.
No don't go in there.
It's too late better get out
quickly or you'll be killed
The plant disactivated.
Damn, did that woman leave me here to
die with that A and bash the stampede?
That wasn't our deal!
I can't believe this is happening, and it
was so hard to get the funds to repair it.
We have to leave.
But Max is still in there, Mom!
Come on, we better be...
What?
The levels are dropping.
But how did that happen?
How should I know?
It can't be.
It couldn't be.
All right! Yes!
Vash! Damn it!
I can't believe it!
Mr.
Vash is alive!
He stopped the plan from
exploding, and he saved us all!
Uh, y-yeah.
Hey, Mr. Vash!
Nice going, Vash!
You're welcome to take
care of this town, old man!
Thank you, Vash!
Aren't you gonna go see him?
He just likes to scare people.
He's so bad.
Come on, Millie, let's go
organize our paperwork.
Huh?
Hey, Meryl! Wait up!
You...how?
I'm very sorry that I didn't die.
I just couldn't allow everyone
in the city to be destroyed.
How dare you?
How dare you say that after what you did?
If you had succeeded in
destroying the plant,
then you would have been the same as me.
I know that, but you're the last
person I want to hear that from.
You destroyed July, you're
nothing but a hypocrite!
I have no memory of any of it.
That ruined city,
with all the piles of debris, were the
first and last things I saw of that place.
It's strange.
I can't remember anything before that,
except for memories of my early childhood.
You're telling me it wasn't you?
I don't know.
Don't know?
Then just let me blame you for it.
Let me have my revenge!
Way to go, Mr. Bash!
The city is safe!
Why did it have to be you?
Why did someone like you have to
turn out to be Bash the Stampede?
I'm sorry.
It couldn't be the same then.
This can't be happening.
It was you all the time.
That can't be, that can't be, no, no.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
dynamite's neon.
The sand steamer will
shake the moment the huge
dynamos on each of his
shoulders start to spark.
In the pitch black darkness
the gruesome party begins.